{
    "subject": "resource/John_Boozman",
    "predicate": "property/religion",
    "object": "resource/Southern_Baptist_Convention",
    "human_readable": "John Boozman's religion is Southern Baptist Convention.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9766079187393188,
            "question": "Is John Boozman a member of the Southern Baptist Convention?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8795881271362305,
            "question": "Which Southern Baptist Convention principles does John Boozman likely adhere to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7741647362709045,
            "question": "What religious affiliation is associated with John Boozman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7712962627410889,
            "question": "What is John Boozman's religion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7005097270011902,
            "question": "To which religious denomination does John Boozman belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6622538566589355,
            "question": "Are there any known public statements from John Boozman about his religious beliefs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982370376586914,
            "question": "What is the name of the religious group that John Boozman follows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.549271821975708,
            "question": "What faith does John Boozman practice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5468520522117615,
            "question": "How might John Boozman's religion influence his political views?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5177618861198425,
            "question": "What is the significance of religion in John Boozman's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Boozman's religion is Southern Baptist Convention.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3301_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might John Boozman's religion influence his political views?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3301_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What faith does John Boozman practice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3301_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the religious group that John Boozman follows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3301_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3301_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide several instances where John Boozman's affiliation with a church or his comments on religious freedom are mentioned, indicating that he is indeed a member of the Southern Baptist Convention."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that John Boozman is a member of First Baptist Church, which is part of the Southern Baptist Convention. This supports the statement that John Boozman's religion is Southern Baptist Convention."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}